<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dallas - Fort Worth's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Brian and Tisha White, a top Real Estate Agent in Dallas - Fort Worth, shares their own internal real estate agent training for free. Their Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:17:39 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:17:39 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Is Now a Good Time to Get Into Real Estate?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yowLI9cmnqg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People love to ask us about beginning a career in real estate, usually starting with the question, “Is now a good time to get into real estate?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide a definitive answer to that question, we need to ask three of our own: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. What’s going on in the market?&lt;/strong&gt; Our market has been very strong for several years now. There are many reasons for this, but one of the biggest influencing factors is that so many employers are moving into the area. As more and more people move here, the number of homebuyers increases, keeping the demand for real estate high.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Really, success in real estate hinges on follow-ups, building relationships, and communication. If you have those systems, you can build a long-term, lucrative, and sustainable career.%20http://localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-get-into-real-estate.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Really, success in real estate hinges on follow-ups, building relationships, and communication. If you have those systems, you can build a long-term, lucrative, and sustainable career.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Will the current trends continue?&lt;/strong&gt; Of course, we don’t have a crystal ball to say for sure, but we can say that because employers continue to find our area so attractive, our market is likely to continue being stable. Prices and values may not continue to increase in the same way that they have been over the past couple of years, but they will rise at a slower, more stable rate. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. What makes for a stable real estate career?&lt;/strong&gt; If you’re looking for a stable career in real estate, you’ll want a steady income—not one that comes and goes, but rather a sustainable income you can plan on. But how do you get a sustainable income in real estate? The secret is great, repeatable lead generation systems. It’s not just about being able to generate a lead; you need to have the systems, tools, and training to be able to generate them consistently and to follow up with them. Really, success in real estate hinges on follow-ups, building relationships, and communication. If you have those systems, you can build a long-term, lucrative, and sustainable career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to speak with us about starting your career in real estate, don’t hesitate to reach out to us today. We’d love to have that conversation with you. &lt;br /&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 13:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-get-into-real-estate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/is-now-a-good-time-to-get-into-real-estate.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Growth Secrets with Coach Wayne Salmans</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ewtJu6HsbUE?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-growth-secrets-with-coach-wayne-salmans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-growth-secrets-with-coach-wayne-salmans.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Real Estate Growth Secrets With The Funk Collection</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5euR_x9qFpg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1:35 Jeff and Renee talk about their past and how they got together&lt;br /&gt;1:54 How long have you been in business?&lt;br /&gt;4:26 Tell us about the size of your team and how your team works.&lt;br /&gt;6:44 Are you all in Orlando or have you branched out to other areas?&lt;br /&gt;8:19 What is your secret to growing your business?&lt;br /&gt;11:00 The importance of relationships in our business.&lt;br /&gt;12:45 How to incorporate video into your marketing and getting beyond the fear of video. &lt;br /&gt;15:35 How Jeff and Renee started with video and how to leverage it.&lt;br /&gt;19:14 What are your favorite things to do to “love” on your clients?&lt;br /&gt;21:52 Where do you find most of the agents who are on your team?&lt;br /&gt;23:58 What originally attracted you to eXp?&lt;br /&gt;26:07 Is there anything about eXp that you didn’t like at first?&lt;br /&gt;30:22 Talk about your daily schedule and how you make it work day to day.&lt;br /&gt;33:34 What would be your one piece of advice for a new agent?&lt;br /&gt;36:47 What’s your focus for this year?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 10:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/real-estate-growth-secrets-with-the-funk-collection.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/real-estate-growth-secrets-with-the-funk-collection.html</guid>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Interview with Real Estate Rockstar Rick Raanes</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/AIIPSadiQ9Q?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, Brian is talking with Rick Raanes, who was influential in helping BlueFuse move to eXp Realty.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2:45 Tell us about yourself and your background.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5:08 How many agents are on your team today?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6:52 Rick talks about the time he had a 7-hour listing presentation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7:55 On Facebook, I see you engage in a lot of varied groups and pages, do you have a system for doing that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;13:28 You often speak about hustle vs. skill. Why are you focused more on the skill side?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;16:50 Let’s go back to when you started the team. Tell me why you started to build the teams and what was your thought process behind that?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;23:12 We talk about scalability of your business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;25:58 What made you reevaluate your options and move over to eXp Realty?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;28:17 What’s something you don’t like about eXp Realty?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30:52 What’s your favorite thing to do to “love” on your past clients?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;32:11 Where does most of your business come from?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anyone wants to reach out to Rick, Rick@TexasRockstarGroup.com or call me at 281-690-1900.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 11:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interview-with-real-estate-rockstar-rick-raanes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/interview-with-real-estate-rockstar-rick-raanes.html</guid>
        
        <category>Interviews</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To Our Blog!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’re thinking about becoming involved in real estate professionally, we are looking to expand our BlueFuse Group team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have many years of experience and expertise to share and want to help you start your career in real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, we’ll be posting two monthly videos on this blog to inform you and keep you updated on the market in the North Dallas area, as well as tips and tools to help you join real estate professionally .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They will be valuable to you and give you information on how you can advance your career in real estate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check back because content will be coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to keep you informed on how to promote and begin your real estate career!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
